A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Departmental Reports, Series 28 FA370
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Departmental Reports, Series 28
1960-1973
Rockefeller Archive Center
New York (State). State Commission for Human Rights
Boyd, Joseph H.
New York (State). Governor (1959-1973: Rockefeller)
Morrow, Hugh
Cannon, James M.
Whitman, Ann
New York (State). Dept. of Civil Service
Ronan, William J. (William John)
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
FA370
5 record cartons
Biographical/Historical note
Nelson A. Rockefeller served as governor of New York from January 1, 1959, to December 18, 1973. He was the first person elected to four consecutive four-year terms as a state governor.
File Plan note
Former Classification: III 15 28
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for scholarly research, except where particular restrictions are noted.
RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
Arrangement note
The reports are arranged alphabetically by department and then chronologically thereunder.
Scope and Contents note
NOTE TO RESEARCHERS
This material in this series documents the official activities of departments, divisions, and agencies of the executive branch of the New York state government during Nelson A. Rockefeller's governorship. The actions, decisions, and exchanges of information or points of view documented here occurred in the course of proposing and implementing policies for the Rockefeller administration. However, unless a document is personally signed by Nelson A. Rockefeller, or is referred to in a document personally signed by him, it should not be assumed that he saw the document or was aware of its existence or substance. Furthermore, researchers should bear in mind that these files may contain documents addressed to Rockefeller which were never shown to him.
SCOPE AND CONTENT
This series consists of periodic reports prepared by departments and agencies of the New York state government for Gov. Nelson A. Rockefeller. The reports are of four different types, from four different periods representing each of Governor Rockefeller's four administrations. In general the reports offer an assessment of each department's responsibilities, goals, performance, problems, and needs. Each of the four different report types is found for most, but not all, of the departments. The four types of reports are as follows:
Program Meeting Report, 1960. Issued in late 1960, these were the result of meetings by representatives of each department with the Secretary to the Governor and the Counsel to the Governor. The purpose of the meeting was to identify the major issues each department would face in the coming year and to define any legislative and budgetary support necessary to meet the issues.
Quarterly Reports, 1963-1966. These were initiated by Governor Rockefeller in March 1963 in response to a fiscal crisis and a "taxpayer revolt" which affected the operation of all departments and construction programs. The reports were to include a one-page "Commissioner's statement," the status of major programs, emergency situations and other unusual developments, and brief summaries of recent research, publications, and management improvement plans. Many of the reports include charts, tables, other graphics, and appendices of departmental publications. The reports were submitted to Dr. William J. Ronan, Secretary to the Governor. Dr. Ronan's staff of Program Associates reviewed the reports and wrote one-page summaries highlighting the most important points and sometimes offering comments on the quality of the report. Copies of the reports, summaries, and a cover letter from Dr. Ronan were then forwarded to Governor Rockefeller, Lt. Gov. Malcolm Wilson, Budget Director Dr. T. Norman Hurd, and Counsel to the Governor Sol Neil Corbin (later Robert R. Douglass). Governor Rockefeller's handwritten comments are found on a few of these reports. The reports begin with the first quarter of 1963. Most agencies reported through the first quarter of 1966. The reason for terminating the reports is not found in this series. Further information on the guidelines for these reports can be found in folder 102, "Reporting Format."
Agency Appraisal Reports, 1970. These reports represent a self-analysis by each agency defining the agency's purpose, the status of its current programs, and its future plans and needs. They are similar to the Program Meeting Reports, but with more depth. The Appraisal Reports were compiled in the summer of 1970 and together they form a detailed snapshot of the executive branch of the New York state government.
Monthly Reports, 1971-1973. Actually issued every four weeks, these reports are short narratives written in memo form by each agency head. The average length is three pages, with no graphics and few appendices. The focus is on immediate issues and activities. The reports were sent to T. Norman Hurd (Director of State Operations, January 1, 1971-August 31, 1972, Secretary to the Governor, September 1, 1972-1975) who reviewed them and identified a few key points from each report in a summary to Governor Rockefeller. Up to a dozen reports were sent to Governor Rockefeller at a time with a one page summary covering all the reports. Points highlighted in the summary were keyed to numbered tabs attached to the reports. These summaries are filed separately in folders 105-107, "Forwarding Memos and Summaries." Many of the summaries bear Governor Rockefeller's handwritten comments. These reports began in March 1971 and the last ones are dated late November or early December 1973, just before Governor Rockefeller's resignation on December 18.
Other Finding Aids note
Detailed finding aids for each series of this collection are available:
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Appointments Office (FA353)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Assembly and Senate Memos (FA354)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Joseph H. Boyd (FA355)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, James Cannon (FA356)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Affirmative Action (N. Lee Cook) (FA357)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Counsel's Office (FA358)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, New York State Committee to Reelect the President (FA359)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Jerry A. Danzig (FA360)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Executive Chamber (FA361)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, 55th Street (FA362)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Issue Books (FA363)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Arthur Massolo (FA364)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Hugh Morrow (FA242)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, New York Office (FA365)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Civil Service Resolutions (Charles H. Palmer) (FA366)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Political Files (FA367)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Press Office (FA368)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Public Relations (FA369)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, William J. Ronan (FA371)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Speeches (FA372)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Diane Van Wie (FA373)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Ann C. Whitman, Gubernatorial (FA374)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Gene Wyckoff (FA375)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, New York Republican State Fund Raising Reports (FA376)
Presidential campaigns -- United States; Political science; New York (State); Political campaigns -- United States; Legislation -- New York (State); New York (N.Y.); International relations -- United States; Latin America; International economic relations; International relations; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1970; Human rights; Arms control; Affirmative action programs -- New York (State); Civil defense; Arms control -- United States; Civil service; Civil defense -- United States; Federal government -- United States; Government policy; Civil service -- New York (State); Economics; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1966; Presidential candidates -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1958; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1962; State governments -- United States; United States; Public policy; Public relations; Vice-Presidents -- United States; New York (State). State Commission for Human Rights; Boyd, Joseph H.; New York (State). Governor (1959-1973: Rockefeller); Republican Party (U.S.: 1854- ); Morrow, Hugh; Cannon, James M.; Whitman, Ann; New York (State). Dept. of Civil Service; Ronan, William J. (William John); Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
- Adirondack Park Agency, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  9 monthly reports, March-November 1973
- Office for the Aging, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 1 semi-annual report, 1972; 19 monthly reports, March 1971 - November 1973
- Department of Agriculture and Markets, 1960, 1963-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Program Meeting Report, 1960; 7 quarterly reports, January 1963 - September 1964
- Department of Agriculture and Markets, 1960, 1963-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  6 quarterly reports, October 1964 - March 1966
- Department of Agriculture and Markets, 1960, 1963-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 35 monthly reports, March 1971 - December 1973
- Division of Alchoholic Beverage Control/State Liquor Authority, 1960, 1963-1966, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Program Meeting Report, 1960; 12 quarterly reports, January 1963 - March 1966
- Division of Alchoholic Beverage Control/State Liquor Authority, 1960, 1963-1966, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 32 monthly reports, March 1971 - December 1973
- New York State Council on Architecture, circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Agency Appraisal Report, circa 1970
- New York State Council on the Arts, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 11 monthly reports, March 1971 - April 1973
- Office of Atomic Development, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  5 quarterly reports, January 1963 - March 1965
- New York State Atomic Research and Development Authority, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Minutes of meeting of September 18, 1963, with 27 attachments including the authority's first annual report for April 1962 - March 1963
- Department of Audit and Control, 1963-1966, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  13 quarterly reports, January 1963 - March 1966; 4 quarterly reports, July 1971 - June 1972
- Banking Department, 1960, 1963-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Program Meeting Report, 1960; 12 quarterly reports, January 1963 - March 1966; Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 22 monthly reports, March 1971 - November 1973
- Bingo Control Commission, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  1 quarterly report, January-March 1963; Annual report for 1963
- Division of the Budget, 1963-1966, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  12 quarterly reports, January 1963 - March 1966
- New York State Commission on Cable Television, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  3 monthly reports, September-November 1973
- New York State Civil Defense Commission, 1963-1965, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  12 quarterly reports, January 1963 - December 1965; Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 1 monthly report, March 1971
- Department of Civil Service, 1960, 1962-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Program Meeting Report, 1960; annual report, 1962; 5 quarterly reports, January 1963 - March 1964
- Department of Civil Service, 1960, 1962-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  3 quarterly reports, April-December 1964
- Department of Civil Service, 1960, 1962-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  4 quarterly reports, January-December 1965
- Department of Civil Service, 1960, 1962-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  1 quarterly report, January-March 1966; Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 36 monthly reports, March 1971-November 1973
- Department of Commerce, 1960, 1963-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Program Meeting Report, 1960; 4 quarterly reports, January-December 1963
- Department of Commerce, 1960, 1963-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  4 quarterly reports, January-December 1964
- Department of Commerce, 1960, 1963-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Department of Commerce, 1960, 1963-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  1 quarterly report, January-March 1966; Agency Appraisal Report, 1970
- Department of Commerce, 1960, 1963-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  37 Monthly reports, March 1971 - November 1973
- Office for Community Affairs, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 1 monthly report, February 1971
- Conservation Department, 1960, 1963-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  2 Program Meeting Reports, 1960; 12 quarterly reports, January 1963 - December 1965
- Conservation Department, 1960, 1963-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  1 quarterly report, January-March 1966; Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 31 monthly reports, March 1971 - November 1973
- State Consumer Protection Board, 1971, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  14 quarterly reports, March 1971 - June 1973
- Department of Correction, 1960, 1963-1964, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  Program Meeting Report, 1960; 8 quarterly reports, January 1963 - December 1964; Agency Appraisal Reports, 1970; 8 monthly reports, March 1971 - December 1971
- Department of Correction, 1960, 1963-1964, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  24 monthly reports, January 1972 - December 1973
- Crime Victims Compensation Board, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  Agency Appraisal Report, 1970
- Division of Criminal Justice Services, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  16 quarterly reports, September 1972 - November 1973
- State Commission Against Discrimination, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  Program Meeting Report, 1960
- Education Department, Bulk, 1963-1965 Bulk, 1963-1965 1960, bulk 1963-1965, 1970-1973; bulk (Box 2, Folder 36)
  Program Meeting Report, 1960; 6 quarterly reports, January 1963 - June 1964
- Education Department, Bulk, 1963-1965 Bulk, 1963-1965 1960, bulk 1963-1965, 1970-1973; bulk (Box 2, Folder 37)
  6 quarterly reports, July 1964 - December 1965; Agency Appraisal Report, 1970
- Education Department, Bulk, 1963-1965 Bulk, 1963-1965 1960, bulk 1963-1965, 1970-1973; bulk (Box 2, Folder 38)
  17 monthly reports, March 1971 - November 1973
- Office of Education Performance Review, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  3 monthly reports, September - November 1973
- Board of Equalization and Assessment, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  1 quarterly report, January - March 1963
- Office of General Services, 1963-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  8 quarterly reports, January 1963 - December 1964
- Office of General Services, 1963-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  5 quarterly reports, January 1965 - March 1966
- Office of General Services, 1963-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 35 monthly reports, March 1971 - November 1973
- Department of Health, 1960, 1963-1966, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  Program Meeting Report, 1960; 8 quarterly reports, January 1963 - December 1964
- Department of Health, 1960, 1963-1966, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Department of Health, 1960, 1963-1966, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  36 monthly reports, March 1971 - November 1973
- Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 1960, 1963-1965, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  Program Meeting Report, 1960; 7 quarterly reports, January 1963 - March 1965; Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 21 monthly reports, March 1971 - December 1973
- Division of Housing and Community Renewal - Office of Rent Administration, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  3 quarterly reports, January 1965 - March 1966
  Related Archival Materials note
  See also Rent Commission.
- Commission/Division of Human Rights, 1963, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  2 quarterly reports, first and third quarters 1963; Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 35 monthly reports, March 1971 - November 1973
- Identification and Intelligence System, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 19 monthly reports, March 1971 - August 1972
- Insurance Department, 1960, 1963-1965, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  Program Meeting Report, 1960; 10 quarterly reports, January 1963 - June 1965
- Insurance Department, 1960, 1963-1965, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 33 monthly reports, May 1971 - November 1973
- Department of Labor, 1960, 1963-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Department of Labor, 1960, 1963-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  6 quarterly reports, October 1964 - March 1966; Agency Appraisal Report, 1970
- Department of Labor, 1960, 1963-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Department of Law, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  11 quarterly reports, January 1963 - September 1965
- Office for Local Government, Bulk, 1963-1965 Bulk, 1963-1965 1960, bulk 1963-1965, 1970-1973; bulk (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Office for Local Government, Bulk, 1963-1965 Bulk, 1963-1965 1960, 1963-1965, 1970-1973; bulk (Box 3, Folder 58)
  Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 36 monthly reports, March 1971 - November 1973
- Manpower Resources Commission, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  2 monthly reports, March - April 1971
- Board of Mediation, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 0059A)
  1 quarterly report, July-September 1963
- Department of Mental Hygiene, 1960, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  Program Meeting Report, 1960; 10 quarterly reports, January 1963 - March 1966
- Department of Mental Hygiene, 1960, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  33 monthly reports, March 1971 - November 1973
- Division of Military and Naval Affairs, Bulk, 1963-1966 Bulk, 1963-1966 1960, bulk 1963-1966, 1970-1972; bulk (Box 3, Folder 62)
  Program Meeting Report, 1960; 13 quarterly reports, January 1963 - March 1966; Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 21 monthly reports, March 1971 - December 1972
- Division of Military and Naval Affairs, Bulk, 1963-1966 Bulk, 1963-1966 1960, bulk 1963-1966, 1970-1972; bulk (Box 3, Folder 63)
  11 monthly reports, January-November 1973
- Department of Motor Vehicles, Bulk, 1963-1966 Bulk, 1963-1966 1960, bulk 1963-1966, 1970-1973; bulk (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Department of Motor Vehicles, Bulk, 1963-1966 Bulk, 1963-1966 1960, bulk 1963-1966, 1970-1973; bulk (Box 3, Folder 65)
  4 quarterly reports, January-December, 1964
- Department of Motor Vehicles, Bulk, 1963-1966 Bulk, 1963-1966 1960, bulk 1963-1966, 1970-1973; bulk (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Department of Motor Vehicles, Bulk, 1963-1966 Bulk, 1963-1966 1960, bulk 1963-1966, 1970-1973; bulk (Box 3, Folder 67)
  Safety Car Program Feasibility Study, 1966
- Department of Motor Vehicles, Bulk, 1963-1966 Bulk, 1963-1966 1960, bulk 1963-1966, 1970-1973; bulk (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Narcotic Addiction Control Commission, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  34 monthly reports, March 1971 - November 1973
- Division of Parole, Bulk, 1963-1965 Bulk, 1963-1965 1960, bulk 1963-1965, 1970; bulk (Box 4, Folder 71)
  Program Meeting Report, 1960; 6 quarterly reports, January 1963 - June 1965; Agency Appraisal Report, 1970
- Office of Parks and Recreation, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  Program Appraisal Report, 1970; 25 monthly reports, March 1971 - December 1973
- Division of Probation, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  10 monthly reports, November 1972 - December 1973
- Division of Public Information, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 73)
- Public Service Commission, Bulk, 1963-1966 Bulk, 1963-1966 1960, bulk 1963-1966, 1970-1971; bulk (Box 4, Folder 74)
  Program Meeting Report, 1960; 13 quarterly reports, January 1963 - March 1966; Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 1 monthly report, October 1970
- Department of Public Works, 1960, 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 75)
- Department of Public Works, 1960, 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 76)
- Department of Public Works - Route 87, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  1 monthly report, February 1964
- Office for Regional Development, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  1 quarterly report, January-March 1963
- Rent Commission, 1960, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  See also Division of Housing and Community Affairs, Office of Rent Administraton.
- Department of State, 1960, 1963-1966, 1970-1971, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 80)
- Department of State, 1960, 1963-1966, 1970-1971, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  5 quarterly reports, January 1965 - March 1966; Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 2 monthly reports, March 1971 and January 1973
- Division of State Police, Bulk, 1963-1966 Bulk, 1963-1966 1960, bulk 1963-1966, 1970-1973; bulk (Box 4, Folder 82)
  Program Meeting Report, 1960; 9 monthly reports, January 1963 - March 1965
- Division of State Police, Bulk, 1963-1966 Bulk, 1963-1966 1960, bulk 1963-1966, 1970-1973; bulk (Box 4, Folder 83)
  1 quarterly report, April-June 1965
- Division of State Police, Bulk, 1963-1966 Bulk, 1963-1966 1960, bulk 1963-1966, 1970-1973; bulk (Box 4, Folder 84)
  3 quarterly reports, July 1965 - March 1966
- Division of State Police, Bulk, 1963-1966 Bulk, 1963-1966 1960, bulk 1963-1966, 1970-1973; bulk (Box 4, Folder 85)
- State University of New York, 1960, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  Program Meeting Report, 1960; 1 quarterly report, January-March 1963; Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 28 monthly reports, March 1971 - November 1973
- Department of Social Services, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  General note
  formerly Department of Social Welfare
- Department of Social Welfare, 1960, 1963-1966 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  later Department of Social Services
- Department of Social Welfare, 1960, 1963-1966 (Box 4, Folder 89)
- Department of Social Welfare, 1960, 1963-1966 (Box 4, Folder 90)
- Department of Taxation and Finance, Bulk, 1963-1966 Bulk, 1963-1966 1960, bulk 1963-1966, 1970-1973; bulk (Box 4, Folder 91)
  Program Meeting Report, 1960; 12 quarterly reports, January 1963 - December 1965
- Department of Taxation and Finance, Bulk, 1963-1966 Bulk, 1963-1966 1960, bulk 1963-1966, 1970-1973; bulk (Box 5, Folder 92)
  1 quarterly report, January-March 1966; Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 36 monthly reports, March 1971 - December 1973
- Department of Taxation and Finance, Bulk, 1963-1966 Bulk, 1963-1966 1960, bulk 1963-1966, 1970-1973; bulk (Box 5, Folder 93)
  Specifications for an Electronic Data Processing System, 1961
- Thruway Authority, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  1 quarterly report, April-June 1966
- Department of Transportation, 1963-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  13 quarterly reports, January 1963 - March 1966; Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 10 monthly reports, March-December 1971
- Department of Transportation, 1963-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  26 monthly reports, January 1972 - December 1973
- Division of Veteran's Affairs, Bulk, 1963-1966 Bulk, 1963-1966 1960, bulk 1963-1966, 1970-1973; bulk (Box 5, Folder 97)
  Program Meeting Report, 1960; 13 quarterly reports, January 1963 - March 1966; Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 10 monthly reports, March-December 1971
- Division of Veteran's Affairs, 1960, 1963-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  22 monthly reports, January 1072 - December 1973
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  4 monthly reports, July-October 1973
- Division of Youth, 1963-1965, bulk 1970, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  6 quarterly reports, January 1963 - June 1964
- Division of Youth, 1963-1965, 1970, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  6 quarterly reports, July 1964 - December 1965; Agency Appraisal Report, 1970; 20 monthly reports, January 1972 - December 1973
- Reporting Format, 1963, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 102)